A Guide to the Virginia Commission on State Governmental Management Records, 1973-1978
Library of Virginia
- Improving State Governmental Management, 1977 January (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Virginia General Assembly, Final disposition of bills of interest, 1977 March (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Enrolled bills, 1977 March (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Alternatives for the consolidation of the Art Commission, 1977 March (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Improving State Governmental Management, 1977 March (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
- Virginia's State Corporation Commission: An analysis of economic regulation in Virginia, 1977 April (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Financial status, 1977 May (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Senator William B. Hopkins' Remarks on the State's Financial Information System, 1977 May (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Interviews regarding Industrial Development, 1977 May (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Commission activities, 1977 May (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Second staff report on the State Corporation Commission: Recommendations on the real location and reorganization of responsibilities, 1977 June (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Commission meetings, 1977 July (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Commission meetings, 1977 August (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Commission meetings, 1977 November (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Governor's Council on Transportation, 1977 November (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Commission's legislative program, ca. 1978 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Review of the Implementation of the program budget process in Virginia, 1978 March (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Office of Administration, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
- General overview of Administration and Finance Reorganization, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Recommended legislation relating to the Secretary of Administration and Finance, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Advantages and Disadvantages of multi-member form and single executive form, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Agency analysis assignments, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
- List of agencies by office, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Questions on agency management, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Agencies selected for review of personnel programs and procedures, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Backdrop analysis for the assessment of State Governmental Services, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Recommendations regarding the Office of Attorney General, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Powers of the State Board of Education, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Board of Education, Functioning, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Budget, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Budget, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Budget and planning, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Clinchco Elementary School: A Case Study, undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Provisions of the Code of Virginia relating to the allocation of the funds of the State Highway Department, undated (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Description of collegial bodies in the areas of Agriculture, Commerce and Labor, undated (Box 12, Folder 38)
- Comments on Capital Outlay Analysis, undated (Box 12, Folder 39)
- The Commission and it's Work (draft), undated (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Questions concerning the Commission, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Outline for presentation to Statewide Conference on Children's Issues, undated (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Constitutional powers of the Governor, undated (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Council on Criminal Justice, undated (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Decision making, undated (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Demand analysis for state services by functional area, undated (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Department of Agricultural and Economic Development, undated (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Department of Air and Water Quality, undated (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Department of Commerce, undated (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Department of Community Development, undated (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Department of Transportation Safety, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Department of Conservation, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Department of Economic Security, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Department of Games and Inland Fisheries, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Recommendations in the Game and Fish Area, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Department of Health, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Housing and Community Development, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Comment on draft legislation to implement proposal to establish a new Department of Housing and Community Development, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Department of Labor and Industry, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Department of Marine Resources, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Department of Recreation and Historic Preservation, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Department of Rehabilitative Services, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Department of Social and Economic Services, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
- An economic and organizational evaluation of Virginia's traffic records system, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Role of State Government in Education, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Employment comparisons, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Environmental agencies consolidation, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Distribution of Executive Branch operating expenditures, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Executive management, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Foundation list, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Fragmentation of responsibility, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Functional groupings, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Political and institutional traditions affecting State Governmental Management, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Proposed statues regarding the Secretary of Human Resources, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Issues in organizing the Commonwealth's Human Resources activities, undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Issues in organizing the Commonwealth's Human Affairs activities, undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Major organizational issues, Human Affairs, undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Land Use Study Commission, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Issues in licensure, undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Keywords for program assignments, undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Land Use Council, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Patrick McSweeny's remarks to St. Paul's Forum, undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Office of Commerce and Resources, undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Questions on the organization of the Marine and Wildlife area of state government, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Draft reports, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Tentative organizational recommendations, undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Organizing the State's Cultural Affairs activities, undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Developing organizational alternatives, undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Principles of organization, undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Subcommittee report on State's Personnel System, undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Narrative statement on procedures for analyzing state program activities, undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Program structure, undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
- List of public appearances, undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Major purpose areas, undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
- Role of public authorities in Virginia government, undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Public Records Act, undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Public Safety, undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Proposed Subcommittee report on Personnel, undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Recommendations, undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Listing of suggested priority recommendations, undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
- The role of state government, undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Sample program structure, undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Meeting with the Secretaries, undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
- Why seven Secretaries?, undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
- Should the state's programs concerned with vocational, occupational, basic and continuing education be consolidated?, undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
- Governmental role, undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Some cautionary observations, undated (Box 13, Folder 57)
- The evaluation, taxation and regulation of Public Utilities, undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
- The Bureau of Banking, undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
- Bureau of Insurance, undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
- The Division of Securities and Retail Franchising, undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Superintendent of Public Instruction, undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
- Objectives for transportation organization and management, undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Transportation policy planning and implementation, undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Recommendations on the creation of a Department of Metropolitan Transportation, undated (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Transportation, undated (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Reports to the Commission, undated (Box 13, Folder 67)
- Virginia Institute of Marine Science, undated (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Working assumptions concerning organization, undated (Box 13, Folder 69)
- LD # 1246, Governor and legal proceedings, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- LD # 1252, Opinions of Attorney General, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- LD # 1240, Attorney General, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- LD #3676, Department of Arts and Humanities, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- LD # 1442, Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- LD # 1786, Secretary of Transportation, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- LD # 1788, Secretary of Education, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- LD # 1790, Virginia State Crime Commission, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- LD # 1792, Virginia Housing Study Commission, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- LD # 1794, Commission on Solid Waste, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- LD # 1796, Commission on Veterans' Affairs, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- LD # 1798, Revenue Resources and Economic Commission, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- LD # 5474, Names and duties of certain State agencies, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- LD # 1238, Appointments and removals by the Governor, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- LD # 5972, Prohibition of the appointment of General Assembly to certain boards and commissions, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- LD # 2552, Secretary of Human Resources, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- LD # 1482, Secretary of Education, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- LD # 1456, Secretary of Transportation, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- LD # 1448, Appointment of Agency heads, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- LD # 1446, Secretary of Public Safety, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- LD # 1230, Department of Management Analysis and Systems Development, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- LD # 1228, Department of Intergovernmental Affairs, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- LD # 1222, Computer Resources Center, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- LD # 7405, Amendment in substitute for House Bill No. 1206, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- General legislation, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- House Bill 1782, Department of General Services, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- House Bill 1638, Organization of human services activities in the counties and cities of the Commonwealth, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- General legislation, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- General legislation, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- House Bill 1525, Budget, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Senate Bill 725, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Senate Bill 28, Budget, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Senate Bill 70, Treasury Board, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Senate Bill 73, Department of Recreation and Historic Preservation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Senate Bill 79, Water Control, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Senate Bill 80, State Highway and Transportation Commission, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Senate Bill 81, Public Transportation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Senate Bill 82, Commissioner of Highways and Transportation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Senate Bill 84, Board and Department of Ports and Waterways, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Senate Bill 85, Transportation and Highway Safety, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Senate Bill 87, Department of Commerce, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Senate Bill 110, Telecommunications Study Commission, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Senate Bill 205/207, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Senate Bill 309, Secretary of Natural Resources, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Senate Bill 667, Appointment of Agency Heads, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Senate Joint Resolution 58, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- House Bill 282, Dept. of Computer Services, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- House Bill 283, Trucks and Ornamentals, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- House Bill 284, Rehabilitative Services, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- House Bill 346, Art Commission, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- House Bill 1206, Health Professions regulation, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- House Bill 1565, Commerce and Licensure, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- House Bill 1629, Housing and Community Development, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- House Joint Resolution 20, Naming of Agencies, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- House Joint Resolution 34, Personnel, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Senate Joint Resolution 97, Fire prevention, 1977-1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Misc., Types of legislation, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Staff memos, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Federal Grants and Contracts, 1973-1978 (Box 17-18)
- Agency Questionnaire, Background material, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Agency correspondence with the Commission forwarding questionnaire, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Various agency communication with the Commission concerning questionnaire, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Employee questionnaire, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Program sheets, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Status reporting and summary sheets, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
- Agency questionnaire responses and instruction forms, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Questionnaire distribution and follow-up sheet, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Preliminary findings sheets, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Agency goals statement sheets, ca. 1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Dept. Agriculture and Commerce, Questionnaires (Program Inventory Forms), 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Dept. of Health, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Dept. of Professional and Occupational Regulation, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Dept. of Labor and Industry, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Soil and Water Conservation Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Virginia Historic Landmarks Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Commission on Game and Inland Fisheries, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Division of Industrial Development, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Council on the Environment, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Marine Resources Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Commission of Outdoor Recreation and Virginia Outdoors Foundation, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Virginia Poultry Products Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Virginia State Crime Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- State Water Control Board, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Regulatory Boards, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Dept. of Health, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Dept. of Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Division of Drug Abuse and Control, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Virginia Office on Aging, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Virginia Council for the Deaf, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Virginia Employment Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Dept. of Welfare, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Gunston Hall Plantation, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Dept. of Community Colleges, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Dept. of Social Services, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- State Dept. of Education, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- State Dept. of Education, Titles I, III, IV, and V, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- State Dept. of Education, Vocational education, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- State Council of Higher Education, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Virginia Museum, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Virginia School at Hampton, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Virginia State Library, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Dept. of Military Affairs, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Law Enforcement Officers Training Standards Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Dept. of Highways, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Highway Safety Division, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Office of Emergency Services, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Virginia Airports Authority, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Virginia Port Authority, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Dept. of State Police, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Compensation Board, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Dept. of Corrections, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Dept. of Property Records and Insurance, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Dept. of Taxation, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Dept. of Treasury, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Division of Automated Date Processing, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Division of the Budget, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Division of Engineering and Building, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Division of Justice and Crime Prevention, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Division of Personnel, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Rehabilitative School Authority, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- State Board of Elections, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Division of State Planning and Community Affairs, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- State Education Assistance Authority, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Virginia Public Telecommunications Council, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Virginia State Crime Commission, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Office of Administration, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Secretary of the Commonwealth, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- State Energy Office, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Office of Volunteerism, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Auditor of Public Accounts, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Office of the Comptroller, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- State Corporation Commission, State Fire Marshall, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Dept. of Welfare, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Senate Joint Resolution No. 96, 1977 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Human Affairs, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Environmental Management, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Manpower and Economic Affairs, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Administration, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Public Protection, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Education, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Misc. Volume I, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Misc. Volume II, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Misc. Volume III, Questionnaires, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Dept. of Accounts, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Office on Aging, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Dept. of Agriculture and Commerce, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Agricultural Products Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Virginia Agricultural Foundation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Air Pollution Control Board, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Virginia Airports Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Dept. of Alcoholic Beverage Control, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Apprenticeship Council, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- The Art Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Division of Automated Data Processing, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Commission of the Arts and Humanities, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Division of the Budget, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Virginia College Building Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Virginia Commission for Children and Youth, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Secretary of the Commonwealth, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Dept. of Community Colleges, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Compensation Board, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Dept. of Conservation and Economic Development, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Division of Consolidated Laboratory Services, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Dept. of Corrections, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Virginia Council for the Deaf, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- School for the Deaf and Blind, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Criminal Justice Officers, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Developmental Disabilities Planning and Advisory Council, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Division of Drug Abuse Control, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Dept. of Education, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- State Education Assistance Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Virginia Education Loan Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Board of Elections, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Office of Emergency Services, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Virginia Employment Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Virginia Energy Office, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Division of Engineering and Buildings, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Council on the Environment, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Office of the Governor, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Gunston Hall Plantation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Dept. of Health, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- State Council of Higher Education, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Highway Safety Division, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Dept. of Highways and Transportation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Historic Landmarks, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Office of Housing, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Housing Development Authority, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Independence Bicentennial Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Industrial Commission, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Division of Industrial Development, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Jamestown Foundation, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Division of Justice and Crime Prevention, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Dept. of Labor and Industry, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Dept. of Law, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Virginia State Library, Information Papers, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 23)